Your relationship with Caloy?
- We don't have a relationship.
- [JORDAN] You don't?
- That's nonsense.
- Really?
[BEA] Do you know I'm getting
in trouble because of you?
Just leave me alone.
Because they think we're accomplices.
I could even go to jail because of you.
So please, I'm begging you.
Please, please. Stay away from me.
[BILLY] What are you doing here?
Can you please talk to your people?
Let the world know that I'm a criminal?!
Do you think you're going to scare me?
Enjoy your freedom
because it won't last long.
And by the way,
orange looks good on you.
Wow!
You're up early, Ms. Supervisor.
I have a lot of work to do as supervisor.
- Hmm? Do your best, dear.
- [CHUCKLES]
I will, like I always do.
All right, take care!
[WOMAN 1] Sorry, Ms. Mercado,
but we can't process your application
without a police clearance.
[WOMAN 2] Miss, you have a pending case?
[WOMAN 3] We can't hire you, Ms. Mercado.
Your involvement with Carlos Toledo
is all over social media.
We don't accept applicants
with connections or ties to criminals.
[PHONE RINGING]
Pres. Do you have any plans later?
[PRECIOUS] Why?
There's something I want to tell you.
Hmm… Okay. Sure.
[PRECIOUS SQUEALING] Lydia!
I think he's planning to confess to me!
Yeah.
I didn't expect things would go this fast
after knowing each other
for only a few weeks.
I'm done second-guessing!
I'm taking the risk!
[LUCY] That's the right decision, Enrico.
You need to tell your children's
mother figure the truth about who you are.
Even if there's a chance
she'll get angry with me
and I won't get to see my children again?
What's important is that you're honest
with the person who loves them.
And with the woman you love.
You love Precious, don't you?
Looks like you've had quite a few.
Not really.
Have you ordered? What do you want?
Oh, nothing. I'm fine.
I'll just have whatever you're having.
Precious, there's something
I need to confess.
[HESITATES]
I'm torn.
I don't know if I should tell you.
I'm afraid you'll get angry.
I won't get angry.
What is it you want to tell me?
[VOICE BREAKING] Precious…
I'm sorry.
But the truth is…
I love you too.
Are we good? Okay?
Okay.
Contact party giveaway supplier.
Confirm orders of flowers
for the centerpiece, okay.
Centerpiece, okay.
Follow up catering
and cake supplier.
Hmm. What should we use?
The function room or the main dining room?
We should do it in the function room.
It's more private there.
Okay.
And let's finalize the menu.
It's going to be tomorrow.
Wait, wait. I want you to
listen to this. Wait.
I think this suits Auntie Pres.
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
- It's perfect.
- Mm.
- I'm good with that.
- Right?
[MUSIC STOPS]
Nice, right?
- It's great. Perfect.
- Mm-hmm.
You know what, dude?
I didn't think Auntie Pres
would fall in love again
after Uncle Rico died
right on their wedding day.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] Even after
everything she went through,
she's always smiling.
She's so strong,
you'd never guess what she's been through.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
But ever since someone
opened her heart again,
Auntie Pres has become happier.
Her smiles are just different.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
She's happy and complete on her own.
But now, she has more reasons to smile.
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOG]
Even if it's uncertain,
many still take risks on love.
Because once it happens,
it'll completely change a person's life.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's a different sense of happiness
when someone loves you.
And when you love someone too.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What?
Nothing.
Is there anyone we forgot to invite?
Hmm…
You might… have someone in mind?
There is one person.
The man who's making Auntie Pres happy.
Should we invite him?
- Sure!
- Mm-hmm.
All right, I'll ask for his number.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
["ABELYANA" BY MAKI PLAYING]
Dude!
What are you doing?!
This can't be.
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
[PLASTIC WRAPPER RUSTLING]
I GOT LOST AGAIN
LIKE I LEARNED NOTHING BEFORE
THOUSANDS OF MILES
I'LL WALK BEFORE GIVING UP
["ABELYANA" CONTINUES]
JUST TO FIND YOU
AND FOR YOU TO FIND ME TOO
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Happy birthday to me.
BILLY: SORRY, AUNTIE PRES.
THERE'S AN EMERGENCY AT THE OFFICE.
I MIGHT GET HOME LATE.
That's it?
No birthday greetings?
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[PRECIOUS] It's a bit sad.
I don't think anyone
remembered my birthday.
I did! I remembered it's today!
Can I take you out to dinner later?
You can.
Billy's working, and Oliver's camping.
And no one else invited me to anything.
[ENRICO] Isn't that better?
It'd be just the two of us.
Okay, sure.
But is it okay if we go to church first?
Yeah, we can meet there.
Is 5:00 p.m. okay with you?
Mm-hmm. [SOFT LAUGH]
Bye.
[MUSIC FADING]
- [MAN] Coach Brandon? You have a call.
- [PHONE RINGING]
[BRANDON] Oh, thanks.
Hello?
Hi. Is this Brandon Enriquez?
Yeah. Who is this?
Hi, this is Billy.
Auntie Precious is my adoptive mother.
All right, so is there a problem?
No. No problem at all.
Um…
It's actually her birthday today.
- So what?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Um, we're having a surprise party for her,
and we were hoping you could come.
Surprise?
She doesn't know you're inviting me?
No.
Aren't you aware that
we're no longer on good terms?
Um…
She did mention a spat you had, but…
surely you've made amends by now.
Nope.
I'll hang up now. I'm busy.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[HANG-UP TONE]
[MUSIC ENDS]
- I've fallen in love with Precious.
- [MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't want to lose
what we have right now.
But I promise,
at the right time,
I'll tell her everything.
[MELLOW MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
So weird.
I really thought Auntie Precious
was going out with Brandon.
Got any idea who the guy is?
She sure knows how to keep a secret.
She didn't tell me a thing!
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let it go.
Thank you for joining me on my birthday.
Even if it wasn't your birthday,
I'd still want to be with you.
Where do you want to eat?
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [STAMMERS]
Excuse me. Oh, I'm sorry.
Give me a second.
Oh.
It's Lydia, my colleague
at Angels of Grace.
She probably just wants to greet me.
Hello? Finally!
Listen, Precious…
Sorry this is so last-minute.
Remember that sponsor
we've been trying to get
for Angels of Grace?
Well, he's finally agreed
to meet with us over dinner!
[GASPS]
Oh, thank goodness!
I've been praying for this
for a long time!
Okay, okay. When?
Well, here's the thing…
My goodness, it's such short notice.
It's tonight,
7:30 p.m. at the Lasap resto-bar.
What?
That's right. And you'll be
the one doing the talking.
You'll explain the advocacies
and programs of Angels of Grace.
Unfortunately, I'm in Batangas,
so I can't be with you there.
Come on.
Just think of the free dinner.
By the way, the reservation is
under Mr. Soriano.
I'm counting on you, okay?
[PRECIOUS HESITATES]
Okay. Okay, sure.
[MOUTHS] I'm sorry.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOUTHS] No worries.
- How was it, Auntie?
- [LYDIA] Oh, total success!
- She said yes.
- Okay?
- Yay!
- She's coming here.
- Yes.
- Auntie…
[LYDIA] What?
Do you know who Auntie Pres is dating?
Hasn't she told you?
The only person she mentioned was Brandon.
But I just called him, and I don't think
they're still seeing each other.
Ah, so you really have no idea.
It's Sir Eric.
Your aunt is dating Sir Eric.
Eric? As in, the same Sir Eric?
Yes, the canteen supervisor
at Oliver's school.
I actually think he's already
close with Oliver.
- Mm-hmm.
[MUSIC BUILDING UP]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MUSIC FADES]
- [TRAFFIC NOISE]
[PRECIOUS] Oh, thank you.
I don't know, I'd probably be
a bother in your meeting.
- It's okay.
- I'll stay outside and wait.
Come with me inside.
It will only be a short meeting.
Okay. But I'll stay
at another table, okay?
If you want us to have dinner
once your meeting is done,
we can have dinner here.
Okay. Anywhere is fine,
as long as I'm with you.
Miss, I have a reservation
with Mr. Soriano.
Yes, ma'am. Please go this way.
Ah, okay.
I'll come with you
to make sure you're not alone.
Okay.
[KEYPAD CLACKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYPAD CLACKS]
[COUNTDOWN TICKING ON PHONE]
- Cute.
- Mm-hmm.
Why didn't Auntie Pres tell us
that she was dating Sir Eric?
Well, didn't she hide
her thing with Brandon before?
- Mm, yeah.
- You just caught her.
Maybe she's still shy about it.
Okay.
Well, if they really are dating,
I hope we can meet him.
- To see if he's any good.
- Let her be.
She's 41 years old.
She knows what she's doing.
- [JORDAN] Relax.
- Okay.
[WOMAN] Oh! Ms. Precious is here!
- [SQUEALS] Okay, okay. Auntie!
- She's here.
- [LYDIA] Everyone, hide!
- Wait. Dude!
- Wait, wait, wait.
- Hide, everyone. Hurry!
- Everyone, quiet. Okay?
- Hurry up, Jordan!
- Surprise!
- [PEOPLE CLAPPING]
- [CHUCKLING]
[PRECIOUS] Billy!
[EVERYONE]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
[PRECIOUS] Billy, you are
behind all this, aren't you?
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday
Happy birthday to you ♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PRECIOUS GASPS]
Billy! Oh my God!
Are you okay?
You know him, Auntie?
[PRECIOUS] Uh…
Yes. That's Sir Eric.
I was planning to
tell you about him, Billy.
Billy, I can explain.
I didn't plan to hide it from your aunt--
You just won't leave us alone.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I only asked for one thing.
Billy--
[BILLY] Just leave.
Stay away from my family.
Billy, what's going on?
How could you be so selfish?
Seriously?
You even made a fool of the person
who raised us and cared for us
when that should have been you?!
He's your father, Billy?
I didn't mean to fool anyone.
Precious…
Leave.
You're a liar!
- Precious…
- I said leave!
Never show your face here again! Leave!
Get out!
Are you okay?
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Pa!
Pa.
[PRECIOUS CRYING]
Billy, I'm sorry.
If I could only choose a father,
I would've done it.
We're tired of waiting
on you, Enrico.
I don't care anymore.
You want to beat me up?
Just kill me!
If you really can't pay
the money back,
I'll get it from your daughter.
[PRECIOUS] What if he
keeps bothering you?
What if he tells Oliver the truth?
Oliver, let's talk.
I know that we made a promise
not to lie to each other.
But I broke that promise.
What do you mean?
You know Sir Eric,
the guy you met at school?